<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<versions>
  <version>
    <number>0.1.2</number>
    <releaseDate>2025-08-02</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>The custom filter for releases can now filter out irrelevant downloaded files at the same time.</item>
      <item>Added sorting by the time a repository is starred.</item>
      <item>Adjusted repository search: currently, entering a keyword triggers real-time repository name matching, while clicking AI Search will retrieve AI-analyzed content, tags, etc., speeding up search. Natural language search is temporarily disabled due to unsatisfactory results.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.1.2-fix</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.1.3</number>
    <releaseDate>2025-08-03</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Add a check for updates feature</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.1.3</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.1.4</number>
    <releaseDate>2025-08-12</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Persistent sorting for repository list</item>
      <item>Added AI detection concurrency configuration</item>
      <item>Unified repository card tag styles</item>
      <item>Improved AI analysis failure indicators and added a retry button for failed items</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.1.4</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.1.5</number>
    <releaseDate>2025-09-23</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>fix: Fixed the issue where the analysis progress becomes 0 due to switching headers during AI analysis</item>
      <item>Add drag and no-drag regions for desktop app</item>
      <item>switch to infinite scroll with consistent card widths</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.1.5</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.1.6</number>
    <releaseDate>2025-10-27</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>fix: Sidebar now scrolls vertically when its content exceeds the screen height, preventing hidden or inaccessible items and improving navigation on smaller screens or long lists.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.1.6</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.1.7</number>
    <releaseDate>2025-11-16</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>fix: Fixed webdav backup recovery issue.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.1.7</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.1.8</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-02-15</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>feat: Supports multiple AI API formats and fixes connectivity testing.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.1.8</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.1.9</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-03</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>feat: Added an optional Express + SQLite backend server, supporting cross-device automatic synchronization.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.1.9</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.0</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-07</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Added optional OpenAI Responses API support while preserving existing OpenAI Chat Completions compatibility.</item>
      <item>Fixed repository update time display and sorting by prioritizing pushed_at, with fallback to updated_at.</item>
      <item>Fixed white-screen crash when opening empty categories by correcting React Hook call order.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.0</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.1</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-07</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Fixed the desktop white-screen startup issue after IndexedDB migration by normalizing persisted state before first render.</item>
      <item>Ensured seamless data migration from legacy localStorage to IndexedDB without requiring users to reset local data.</item>
      <item>Kept rollback compatibility so users can return to older versions without losing existing data.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.1</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.2</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-07</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Added category lock support in repository edit panel to prevent sync from overwriting manual category choices.</item>
      <item>Manual category changes now auto-enable lock by default, and users can still manually unlock later.</item>
      <item>Improved edit modal defaults by preferring AI summary as editable custom description content.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.2</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.3</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-08</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Added repository unstar support and improved delete flow stability by handling 204 No Content responses and cleaning related release/subscription state.</item>
      <item>Fixed desktop first-login token paste issue (Ctrl/Cmd + V) in v0.2.0-v0.2.2 builds.</item>
      <item>Restored global search shortcuts and desktop Edit menu roles (cut/copy/paste/select all) for consistent keyboard behavior.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.3</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.4</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-14</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Improved sync stability, backend auth handling, and mobile layout refinements. (Thanks @HuberttFox for the contribution.)</item>
      <item>Added a release list unsubscribe action with confirmation and immediate sync.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.4</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.5</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-16</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Fixed macOS App/Window menu missing in desktop build, restoring Command+Q (quit) and Command+W (close window) shortcuts.</item>
      <item>Fixed SyntaxError in generated main.js caused by improper string escaping in the build workflow.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.5</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.6</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-22</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Kept already loaded repository cards visible during sync, so refreshes no longer interrupt reading flow.</item>
      <item>Preserved scroll position after repository sync to avoid sudden jumps in long lists.</item>
      <item>Persisted repository view context, including the selected category and current view, across refresh and reload.</item>
      <item>Updated the app and login icon assets to use the project icon consistently.</item>
      <item>Improved nginx proxy resilience for containerized deployments by using a more reliable backend upstream setup. Thanks to external contributor @HuberttFox for PR #60.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.6</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.7</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-25</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Added optional reasoning effort support for GPT-5 compatible OpenAI APIs.</item>
      <item>Kept backward compatibility by leaving reasoning disabled unless users explicitly enable it.</item>
      <item>Persisted the reasoning setting across frontend config state, backend config APIs, import/export, and database migration.</item>
      <item>Improved compatibility for OpenAI Responses and reasoning-enabled requests with longer request and connection test timeouts.</item>
      <item>Normalized legacy unsupported reasoning value `minimal` to `low` to prevent request failures with GPT-5 compatible models.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.7</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.8</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-03-25</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Added observable decryption failure handling for stored AI API keys, WebDAV passwords, and GitHub tokens.</item>
      <item>Kept settings APIs responsive even when one stored secret cannot be decrypted, instead of failing the entire response.</item>
      <item>Returned per-secret status metadata so the frontend can distinguish normal, empty, and decrypt-failed states.</item>
      <item>Added clear Settings warnings telling users to re-enter and save configurations whose stored secrets can no longer be decrypted.</item>
      <item>Improved debugging by logging decryption failures with config context on the backend.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.8</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.2.9</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-04-02</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Improved AI summary parsing by stripping fenced JSON code blocks before extraction.</item>
      <item>Replaced fragile greedy JSON matching with balanced-brace parsing to better handle wrapped responses.</item>
      <item>Increased the AI analysis token budget to reduce failures caused by truncated structured output.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.2.9</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.3.0</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-04-10</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Added hide/show for built-in categories - default categories can be hidden from sidebar and restored from Settings.</item>
      <item>Added delete support for custom categories without affecting repository starred status.</item>
      <item>Added drag-and-drop category assignment - drag repository cards onto sidebar categories to quickly assign.</item>
      <item>Added category lock - manually assigned categories won't be changed by subsequent AI analysis or sync.</item>
      <item>Added AI category matching - AI analysis now considers custom categories and assigns repositories accordingly.</item>
      <item>Fixed Gemini connection test failures by increasing maxTokens threshold. Thanks to @Minttc for the contribution!</item>
      <item>Fixed DeepSeek Reasoner compatibility by removing unsupported API parameters.</item>
      <item>Fixed sidebar layout - category count badges are now properly aligned without layout shifts on hover.</item>
      <item>Fixed backend persistence - category lock state is now properly synced to the database.</item>
      <item>Fixed category rename - renaming a custom category now updates all assigned repositories.</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.3.0</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.4.0</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-04-18</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Tabbed Settings Interface: Settings are now organized into dedicated panels (General, AI, WebDAV, Backup, Backend, Category, Data Management) with mobile-friendly tab navigation.</item>
      <item>Repository Multi-Select and Bulk Actions: Select multiple repositories at once with a bulk actions toolbar, bulk categorization modal, and pipelined AI-summary bulk processing.</item>
      <item>README Modal: View repository READMEs with an improved Markdown renderer featuring safer link and image handling.</item>
      <item>Back-to-Top Button: Quick navigation for long lists.</item>
      <item>WebDAV Backup/Restore: Backup your data to WebDAV and restore when needed.</item>
      <item>Backend Sync Controls: Sync your data across devices with backend integration.</item>
      <item>AI Config Management: Configure and manage AI service settings.</item>
      <item>Preset Asset Filters: Quick filter presets for release assets.</item>
      <item>Category Management and Ordering: Organize categories with drag-and-drop reordering.</item>
      <item>Settings Refactor: Settings split into focused subpanels for better organization.</item>
      <item>New UI utilities and animations (scrollbars, touch helpers, slide/shake/bounce effects).</item>
      <item>README decoding now preserves UTF-8 encoding.</item>
      <item>More robust Markdown and link handling.</item>
      <item>Special thanks to @SummerRay160 for their tremendous contributions to this release!</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.4.0</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.5.0</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-04-20</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>AI Configuration Panel: Added connection testing for AI services to validate availability before use.</item>
      <item>Prompt Management: Enhanced prompt editing and display logic with better management experience.</item>
      <item>Default Category Override: Modify name, icon, and keywords for default categories with reset functionality.</item>
      <item>Category Keywords: Added keyword support for categories with keyword input during creation/editing.</item>
      <item>Trending View: New navigation entry with four channels - Most Stars, Most Forks, Top Developers, and Trending.</item>
      <item>Batch AI Analysis: Reuse AIAnalysisOptimizer for subscription content with pause/resume/stop controls.</item>
      <item>Backend Proxy: New Search API proxy routes for backend mode supporting GitHub Search.</item>
      <item>Trending Filters: Time-range (daily/weekly/monthly) and language input for trending discovery.</item>
      <item>Improved responsive layout for better mobile and desktop adaptation.</item>
      <item>Full Chinese and English localization for all trending channels.</item>
      <item>Fixed merge conflicts and tag rendering issues in subscription feature.</item>
      <item>Special thanks to @SummerRay160 (PR #84, #85) and @chan-yuu (PR #86) for their contributions!</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.5.0</downloadUrl>
  </version>
  <version>
    <number>0.5.2</number>
    <releaseDate>2026-04-24</releaseDate>
    <changelog>
      <item>Discovery View Refactor: Replaced subscription view with a new Discovery view featuring channel-based browsing, multi-filter sorting, search, pagination, and a "Load more" button. (PR #90)</item>
      <item>Enhanced Markdown renderer with syntax highlighting, copyable code blocks, image zoom/modal, in-modal TOC, heading navigation, and adjustable font size. (PR #90)</item>
      <item>Added in-page AI analysis controls for repository cards with star/unstar support and safer clipboard helpers. (PR #90)</item>
      <item>Improved responsive layout with Inter font family, refined breakpoints, and lucide-react icons throughout. (PR #90)</item>
      <item>Switched Trending data source from GitHub Search API to GitHubTrendingRSS for more reliable results, with daily/weekly/monthly time-range filter. (PR #96)</item>
      <item>Added RSS description parsing with HTML entity decoding, and supplemented RSS data with GitHub API for missing repository fields. (PR #96)</item>
      <item>Fixed macOS desktop white-screen crash by removing Inter/CDN stylesheet loading and hardening discovery state rehydration. (PR #95)</item>
      <item>Removed auto-loading pagination from Discovery view and fixed null/empty description handling in RepositoryEditModal. (PR #97)</item>
      <item>Special thanks to @SummerRay160 for their outstanding contributions to this release (PR #90, #97)!</item>
    </changelog>
    <downloadUrl>https://github.com/AmintaCCCP/GithubStarsManager/releases/tag/v0.5.2</downloadUrl>
  </version>
</versions>
